THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
- Salute! - Salute!
I think the fold on these napkins is a little off.
I'll correct it.
Don't forget. The table setting is just as important as the food.
- Yes, Chef! - We're short on time. Let's move.
- Finish the prep thoroughly. - Yes, Chef!
I'm thinking of searing it to about this point
So what do you think would be a good garnish?
This meat isn't cooked evenly.
I'll show you one time, so watch carefully.
- Is this that difficult? - You're brilliant, Chef.
- Hey. - Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun!
- Can't you wash the dishes properly? - I'm sorry.
Do you feel pathetic washing dishes now that you're a sergeant?
- No, sir. - Let's do a better job.
- Understood? - Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun!
Kang Seong-jae.
- Seong-jae. - Gosh.
- Kang Seong-jae. - What?
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
What were you dreaming about to be grinning like that?
You punk. Your discipline's slipping.
- Get up. It's time for your shift. - Yes, I understand.
Get ready. Hurry.
Yes, I understand.
WARNING: YOUR CHILDREN ARE IN OPERATIONS
EPISODE 10
Current troop count for Ganglim Outpost.
29 total, 3 on leave, 26 present.
Personnel returning from leave report no incidents of note.
- Okay. Next. - Equipment check results.
The Thermal Observation Device is operating normally.
- Next. - Guard patrol, nothing to report.
However, the CCTV at Outpost Three
Has a blind spot that needs to be adjusted.
A request has been submitted to the facilities department.
You were supposed to report to me first before putting in a request.
Oh, it was an urgent issue, so I took action first.
No matter how urgent the issue
You were still supposed to report to me first.
Are you trying to make it look like
The Company Commander is being kept in the dark?
I'm sorry. I will report to you first next time.
Man.
You call a meeting first thing in the morning, and for what?
Why is the atmosphere so tense? Deputy Outpost Commander.
Report the training schedule quickly now.
Understood. Next Tuesday, before noon
Regarding the soldier's human rights, the education program...
- Salute, Company Commander! - What is it? We're in a meeting.
What is it?
You should come to the mess hall right away.
When was this cleaned?
Last night, sir.
Are you telling me a fridge cleaned last night
Should have this much frost in it?
Well, because the kitchen temperature rises during cooking...
Well, it seems to form even if we clean it frequently.
Is that supposed to be an excuse?
You can't even maintain a refrigerator
Yet you complain about the food supplies.
You might have thought you could run your mouth
Without consequence as a civilian
But in the army, you need to understand the weight of your words
Before you decide to speak. Don't you think?
Oh, you're here.
Just as you wished, we're conducting a comprehensive inspection
Under the Regimental Commander's orders.
I trust we'll have your full cooperation.
It's about time for the supply truck. Let's all have a look.
Just how poor their condition is.
Grade A green onions from Jindo, South Jeolla Province.
Grade A onions from Muan, South Jeolla Province.
These look like they're in perfect condition with no blemish.
So where are these terrible supplies you mentioned?
These are in much better condition than the vegetables we've been receiving.
Previously, many parts were spoiled, so we often had to throw them away.
So, do these look to be in bad condition to you?
These are photos of supplies that had issues during inspection.
It wasn't just once or twice.
Their condition has been consistently poor.
If you maliciously pick photos like these to show me
You can make it seem like there are problems that don't exist.
I trust what's right in front of me
More than a hundred photos.
I wish to formally object to this comprehensive inspection process itself.
As for the officer in charge of the supplier
I must question whether it's appropriate for you to be conducting this yourself.
Hey!
You've got a strange way of putting things.
So you're implying that I have ulterior motives
For conducting this comprehensive inspection?
We will now conduct an inspection of not just the mess hall
But all personnel at Ganglim Outpost.
I will be completely objective and thorough
So you are to cooperate fully.
Man, he came here on a mission. He's dead set on it.
We could've just let this go quietly.
Why did you have to blow it up like this?
Okay, notify the soldiers still at the Outpost about the inspection.
- Move it! - Yes, sir.
My goodness. You think you can do whatever you want
Just because you're at an outpost? Right?
- Which barrack is this? - Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol, Barracks 2.
Everyone in Barracks 2 receives a demerit.
- Deputy Outpost Commander. - Hold on, let's clean up first.
What do you think you're doing?
Just like you wanted
I investigated all factors hindering
The improvement of the soldiers' meals.
And it turns out there are a whole lot of problems, aren't there?
You think I like cracking down on my own men?
But still
The higher-ups need to know what the problem is.
A soldier must always know
The weight and significance of their words
Before they dare to speak.
I hope you finally learn that this time.
All right.
You need to come with us.
GANGLIM OUTPOST
What? Where is the Outpost Commander going?
Looks like she's in some serious trouble.
We're doomed. Our leave is going to be restricted for a while.
- Darn it. - Hey, it's cold. Let's go in.
I spoke firmly to the supplier
So there won't be any more problems with the provisions.
And Cho Ye-rin is under investigation by the inspection team.
- Min-gu. - Yes, Battalion Commander.
Because you didn't properly handle the things you were supposed to
- the damage has been considerable. - I'm sorry, sir.
I'll try my best to stop any word from getting out of Ganglim...
How badly did you screw up
For word to get out of Ganglim, of all places?
You know the situation.
It's because those pathetic punks, Cho Ye-rin and Kang Seong-jae
Kept getting in the way...
- I'm sorry, sir. - Head up. Back straight.
Is a soldier supposed to hang his head?
- No, sir. - Min-gu.
If it's gotten to the point where even a regular soldier is filing a complaint
Then this isn't something we can just brush aside, right?
I don't think Kang Seong-jae really knows anything.
He just saw Cho Ye-rin complain about the provisions a few times
And is probably repeating what he saw.
What about Cho Ye-rin? How much do you think she knows?
While she was looking into Bonggil Trading
She found out that at the factory's address
There's a junkyard instead of a factory.
What are you talking about?
- Sir, I was going to report it. - Why didn't you report it to me?
She only confirmed it was a junkyard and left
So I decided it wasn't a big deal.
I told you I'm the one who makes that decision!
Cho Ye-rin goes all about whenever it comes to Major Im.
If you're this sloppy
Do you think she would just let it slide?
FIRST LIEUTENANT CHO YE-RIN
I found what she had on her and took it.
I will take responsibility and take care of this matter.
Let's do this right.
I...
Used to love how you were
Like a cornered rat that would even bite the cat.
But you don't have that fire in you anymore.
Please.
Please trust me one last time.
I don't want to be disappointed again.
Major Lee Min-gu.
IM SEUNG-BIN
Why were you investigating the food supply company?
- Like I've said repeatedly... - Did a superior give you the order?
I acted on my own. But...
What were you looking into, leaving your area of operations
During duty hours without reporting it?
Seeing as you know my every move
- you must've been investigating me. - First Lieutenant Cho.
You're here to be investigated.
Then stop trying to railroad us and conduct a proper investigation.
Well, who told you to leave your area of operations?
It was just a little frost in the fridge.
Darn it.
My goodness.
What's the use of talking to someone
Who's determined to find fault with everything?
He's even complaining about
Why the Company Administrative Office needs a portable stove.
I swear, I couldn't help but laugh.
Master Sergeant Park, I'm sorry. This is my fault.
It's all right. You didn't know any better, did you?
He came here determined to tear this outpost apart.
I hope the Outpost Commander will be okay.
Gosh. The Support Section Chief is running amok.
And I'm just standing there taking it.
It makes my blood boil.
This is when the Company Commander should step up
And give him a piece of his mind.
A guy who loves to talk like him
Is just standing there with nothing to say.
That's because the Battalion Commander favors the Support Section Chief
Over our Company Commander, so he can't say a thing, right?
Good grief.
This whole outpost is on their bad list now.
Darn it. Hey, Yoon Dong-hyun.
Why are you boiling the plastic parts too?
Is that what you've been doing this whole time?
Hurry up and take it out!
It's all melting! You idiot. Darn it.
Did you learn nothing over all that time working here?
Regarding the full investigation
I have no excuse for what happened, Battalion Commander.
Especially regarding Ye-rin...
Do you think I called you here just to discuss that? Between us?
I told you before that I'm being transferred to Army Headquarters, right?
Yes, you mentioned it before.
- Is it confirmed? - Yes.
Congratulations, sir.
No need for congratulations. I'm actually worried.
It'll be another dog-eat-dog fight for positions when I get there.
And I want to bring one of my own people with me.
I'd like that person to be you.
What, you don't like the sound of that?
No, that's not it.
You did mention it once before
But I just assumed you would be taking Min-gu with you, so...
Min-gu.
Maybe because I spoiled him
But he's gotten too big for his britches.
He doesn't just say, "Yes, sir" anymore.
That's why you've been on my mind. I raised you with a stricter hand.
Though my abilities are humble
If I can be of service to you, Battalion Commander
- I will do my utmost. - Good.
Then there's just one favor I need to ask.
Yes, sir. Please tell me.
I'm thinking this might be a good chance to clean up Ganglim.
Clean it up? What do you mean?
GANGLIM OUTPOST FACILITY SAFETY INSPECTION REPORT
COMPLETE SHUTDOWN OF THE OUTPOST IS REQUIRED
Submit a few reports up the chain
That there are concerns about accidents due to the outpost's deterioration
And then merge it with another outpost. How about it?
I've shown you how much I trust you
So now I need you to do the same for me, Seok-ho.
Hero.
A spoonful is better than a hundred words.
QUEST: PERSUADE THE REGIMENTAL COMMANDER
Persuade the Regimental Commander with food.
GOURMET RATING
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae is guilty!
I have to persuade the Regimental Commander?
- Hey, Kang Seong-jae. - Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
- What are you doing? Are you done? - Yes, sir.
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun, what if, hypothetically...
No hypotheticals.
Well... Yes, sir.
What is it?
I said
That a delicious meal made from the heart
Has the power to move people, didn't I?
A delicious meal made from the heart
Has the power to move people.
- You're talking nonsense. - My father said that.
As if I could forget the precious, wise words
Your father said. How could I? So, why?
Do you really believe the food I make
Has that kind of power?
Well...
The timing might have been ridiculously perfect
But there's one thing I've realized
From eating all this good food, thanks to you.
That it definitely has some kind of power.
The moment you put the food in your mouth
You just relax, and this feeling rushes over you.
Are you saying ingredients to the Officers' Mess
And the Mess Hall are different?
Let's not mess around when it comes to food.
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun, about our Outpost Commander.
What if I go and ask the Regimental Commander myself?
Ask for what?
My goodness. You're going to get yourself in big trouble.
The Regimental Commander isn't a friend from the neighborhood.
He's not the kind of guy who grants favors
Just because we ask.
Besides, what would you even say, just showing up out of the blue?
Just randomly beg, "Please help our Outpost Commander?"
- Is that your plan? - So I was thinking
- I'd give him some food while I... - My goodness.
Hey, Kang Seong-jae.
Officers live in their own world that we know nothing about.
You get it?
Jeez.
I, the Company Commander
Have awakened.
- Rice! Can I get more rice? Rice! - Hey, Kang Seong-jae.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae. - At the promotion party.
The Regimental Commander went crazy for your japchae, right?
- Is that true? - Yes, he really loved it.
Are you confident?
Yes, I think I can do it.
Come on, that's a bit much.
As if Regimental Commander would spare the Outpost Commander
Over some food Kang Seong-jae made.
- That's ridiculous, sir. - Darn, I would just...
Stop saying it's impossible and use your brain.
What's the point of having a good head if you don't use it?
He never comes to the outpost.
How are we supposed to meet him and what would we do?
Then couldn't we go to where the Regimental Commander is?
If we leave the Outpost, who's going to stand watch and cook?
Besides, that's desertion, you punk.
I see.
Oh, I've seen the Regimental Commander at religious activities, sir.
That's right, religious activities.
We can ask to be sent out for them on the weekend.
- What's your religion again? - I'm Catholic, sir.
Perfect. Catholic church it is.
But what dish are you going to make for him?
Oh, well...
Oh, right. I heard that the Regimental Commander
Is completely crazy about his daughter.
That's right. I overheard guys from the regiment talking
When I went to the battalion for some gear.
Perfect! We just have to win over his daughter.
And when it comes to charming the ladies
Isn't that your specialty, Kang Seong-jae?
Pardon me?
Come on, Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun. When it comes to the ladies...
Well, you want me to give you a tip?
Women like sweet chocolate cookies.
Am I wrong?
But at the outpost
How are we supposed to make chocolate cookies?
Dessert and other cooking recipes are now available.
CHOCOLATE COOKIES
- First, sift the cocoa powder. - I'll just put this here, okay?
- Oh, yes, that's right. Thank you. - All right.
Could you possibly melt the butter for me?
- Sure. - Thank you, sir.
It's melted.
Thank you.
- How long? - One minute, twice, should do it.
Come in.
- Salute! - What is it?
Master Sergeant Park, please let us go for religious activities.
Religious activities? Since when have you ever gone to those?
We'd like to pray.
Amen.
Hey, this has to be the church
The Regimental Commander comes to every Sunday, right?
Yes, I think it is.
Okay. Hey, you need to be careful with this.
- Yes, sir. - Okay, let's go.
Hands together.
Our Brother Bae Gabriel always used to sing louder than anyone.
I suppose his daughter is still not doing very well.
She's about six years old now, isn't she?
Yes.
For the past few days, she hasn't been eating well
And no matter what nice things I bring her
She just turns her head away.
The doctor says there's nothing wrong
But as her father, I can't help but wonder if she's sick
Or if I'm doing something wrong because I don't know any better.
That's all I think about every night.
My goodness. They said the Regimental Commander
Adores his daughter, but he's a total softie for her.
He really does love her so much.
- Shall we pray for your daughter? - Yes.
- Lord. - Attention! Salute!
- Salute! - Salute!
- Salute! - Salute.
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun.
- I'm Joseph. Yoon Joseph. - Oh, are you?
Oh, aren't you Private First Class Kang Seong-jae?
I didn't know you were Catholic.
Oh, yes, sir. I am.
No need to be so formal.
We're all brothers and sisters here, aren't we?
Yes, you're right. Well, earlier
I happened to overhear you talking about your daughter.
And it sounds like you're very worried.
She's usually such a good eater
But she's barely eaten anything lately.
It's been hard on me, too.
Oh, no.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
- What's this? - I made this to give to your daughter.
For my daughter, So-yul?
Hey. Are you here, So-yul?
Oh, this is my wife. And my daughter, So-yul.
GOURMET RATING
- Say hello. - Oh.
Hello.
So... Ms. So-yul... So-yul is very cute.
She's not one to skip a meal
But seeing her like this, I've lost my appetite lately, too.
Oh, right. You said you prepared that for my So-yul?
Let me see what it is.
- Oh, this. - Why did I even bring this...
- Gosh, you brought this? - Yes.
No.
I think there's been a slight misunderstanding.
Come on, you guys, making me feel so awkward...
-Well then, I'll be going. -Yes, sir.
- Salute. - Salute.
FRONT LINE IRONCLAD DEFENSE INVINCIBLE GANGLIM OUTPOST
My goodness. This is not easy at all. His daughter was a dog.
This is going to be completely different from cooking for a person.
If we give up now, the Outpost Commander will...
What are we supposed to do to win over
A picky little princess's heart now?
If we don't know what she likes
- shouldn't we prepare everything? - How?
First of all, we need more help.
Help?
What were you thinking, going there by yourselves?
One wrong move
And it's not just your military careers
But starting with the Company Commander
Everyone down the line gets totally screwed.
But we can't let the Outpost Commander be wronged like this, can we?
- What? - It was like that with the defector
And when Assemblyman Kang came. In the end
A heartfelt dish was what changed people's minds.
So?
I'll win over
The Regimental Commander or at least his dog.
- My goodness. - If you help us
I think we can pull it off.
Master Sergeant Park.
You've tried the food Seong-jae made, haven't you?
Hey, forget the food.
What's all this about winning a dog's heart...
My goodness.
Man, you guys are hopeless, really. I don't know. Whatever.
You know what kind of person
The Outpost Commander is better than anyone, sir.
Hey, what are you doing? Grab this.
- Oh, man, this is heavy. Goodness. - Yes.
Goodness.
Good grief, this is so heavy.
CHICKEN BREASTS, COD FILLET
What is all this?
I didn't know what the Regimental Commander's dog would like.
- So I brought meat, seafood, and poultry. - My gosh.
Thank you, sir.
Of all the things in my life, making food for a dog...
Don't be like that.
Well, anyway, just do your thing and...
- What was the dog's name again? - So-yul.
Right. Make something that So-yul will like.
Yes, sir.
I wonder if this will work.
GREASY COOKED FOOD!
Greasy cooked food.
Warning. Greasy food is dangerous for dogs.
I see.
What? Oh, man, this is delicious!
MEATBALLS
DOG MEATBALLS
Dog meatballs.
Okay.
MIX MINCED PORK, VEGETABLES, RICE FLOUR, AND EGG
BELL PEPPER AND CHICKEN MEATBALL INGREDIENTS: BELL PEPPER, CHICKEN
PORK AND ZUCCHINI MEATBALL INGREDIENTS: PORK, ZUCCHINI
BEEF AND SWEET POTATO MEATBALL INGREDIENTS: BEEF, SWEET POTATO
COD AND POTATO MEATBALL INGREDIENTS: COD, POTATO
BEEF, PORK, AND CARROT MEATBALL INGREDIENTS: BEEF, PORK, CARROT
Pan-fried dog meatball.
PAN-FRIED DOG MEATBALL
All right.
Not enough. She won't eat something like this.
- What do you think of this size? - Yes, I think they're perfect.
Your proficiency in Desserts and Other Dishes
Has increased. Level Up!
Kang Seong-jae's Homemade Dog Treats.
WORTH THREE MICHELIN STARS!
Due to your proficiency, half a star has been added.
Gosh, that smells insane. What is this?
Man, you really put your all into this.
Don't you think even Lady So-yul will be moved by this?
Yes.
Amazing.
Company, attention!
- Salute! - Salute.
Well, fancy seeing you here, Regimental Commander.
Oh, you're the 4th Company Administration and Supply NCO.
For today, I'm just Brother Paul Park.
Oh, you too?
Yes.
Hey, you think she'll eat it?
SO-YUL, THE GOURMET DOG
This is the finest boiled pork.
No, wait, hold on a second.
- Just a taste... - Next!
This is grilled lobster.
Hey, wait, please try this. It's from the coast...
I'm not sure if you'll like what I've made.
APPROVED
She's eating.
My So-yul is eating.
It's the first time in days I've seen her eat so well.
Was it that good?
Well, look at her. Showing her belly to just anyone.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae!
I thought you only knew what people liked to eat
But you've completely mastered the canine palate as well.
Since your daughter is a picky eater
I did research on her preferences, and as a result
It seems she prefers the highest-grade Korean beef round.
I will also gave the recipe to your wife so So-yul...
So I hope your daughter can enjoy her mealtimes too.
Some people might think she's just a dog
But to me, she's really like a daughter to me.
Everyone says I'm making a big deal out of nothing when I say that
But you, Private First Class Kang Seong-jae
Truly understood how I feel. Thank you so much.
I doubt you came all this way for nothing.
You must have something to discuss.
Well, actually...
We came because we have something to tell you, Regimental Commander.
- What is it? - Well, it's just a little...
Honey.
Kang Seong-jae. Go on, tell him.
It's about what I mentioned at the last promotion party.
It's regarding the issue with the food supplies.
You'd know that better than anyone, right?
The condition of the food supplies coming into Ganglim Outpost
Was admittedly not good. However, while they were bad
The quality suddenly improved right before the full inspection.
- Go on. - Well...
A full inspection should be objective and transparent by nature.
And the Support Section Chief in charge of the food supply company says
He will investigate the issue himself. That doesn't make sense.
And it's awfully suspicious
That the quality suddenly got so much better that day.
So, do these look to be in bad condition to you?
Honestly, the food supplies at the Outpost
Were a mess, so they just said so.
And just for saying that
They turn the entire outpost upside down
And drag away the Outpost Commander.
After that, who's going to be able to speak their mind?
How desperate must the men have been
To try and save their Outpost Commander
That they even made dog treats, just... Gosh.
I mean, they came all this way
After making snacks for your daughter.
To be honest
This is my first time in a church in ten years.
Please, reconsider this carefully, Regimental Commander.
Is that true, Private First Class Kang Seong-jae?
Yes, sir!
Yes, it's me.
Bring me all the documents related to the full inspection
Run an additional investigation on the food supplier
And find out what connection they have to Lee Min-gu.
Well done.
- You worthless maggot. - I'm sorry, sir.
You just made Major and you're already
- screwing things up like this? - I'm sorry, sir!
What are you going to do now?
The Regimental Commander gave the order himself.
How am I supposed to stop this?
You said you'd handle it. Is this what you call handling it?
Keep your mouth shut during the investigation.
Do whatever you can to make sure this ends with you.
- Battalion Commander. - This...
If you can't make this end with you
This whole business with Major Im will blow up uncontrollably.
Can you handle that?
I will step up to the plate and take care of this matter.
Do you want me to make Major Im's life a living hell?
If the story about Major Im gets out, there will be no turning back.
I'll take care of it
At my level.
Now you finally seem to understand me.
Lee Min-gu. I'll save you, one way or another.
Darn it!
HANBONG FACTORY, CEO YOON CHEOL-HYEON
Get rid of all the documents in there
And don't let anyone in.
When I tell you to do something, just do it. What's with all the talk?
What do you think you're doing?
From selecting the supplier to managing them
You planned this all by yourself?
You can keep exercising your right to remain silent
But it'll all come out when the investigation results are released.
Battalion Commander. Regarding the Support Section Chief
Being directly involved in selecting the supplier
And evidence suggesting he received kickbacks
Were you aware of that?
I knew nothing about it.
Then...
Do you believe the Support Section Chief acted alone?
I suppose if it's a matter of responsibility
Then it's mine for failing to manage my subordinate.
But if I had known about this beforehand
I would've stopped it one way or another.
About Lee Min-gu. Apparently, he colluded with the company
Signed a secret contract and took bribes...
- He was a real scumbag, apparently. - I knew it.
Ugly on the outside, ugly on the inside. Right?
Anyway, guys who mess around with food
Deserve to fall into the fires of hell!
They deserve divine punishment, sir.
That's right! They deserve divine punishment! Yes!
Hot! Oh my, so hot!
Darn it! They really deserve to be punished.
Do you have any idea how hard I worked to kill those news stories?
I'm so ashamed I can't even face my superiors.
How in the world are you people running things
That crooks lining their own pockets keep popping up?
I'm sorry. I'll make sure this doesn't happen again.
- 4th Company Commander. - Captain Hwang Seok-ho.
During the full-scale investigation, if you found anything suspicious
You should've reported it to me first.
Why are you making a soldier come and report
This kind of problem to me directly?
I'm sorry.
Even though you say it's an individual's misconduct
The higher-ups are keeping a close eye on this matter
So walk on eggshells for a while. Got it?
- Yes, understood. - Yes, understood.
- Salute! - Salute!
I treated him well, but I guess no good deed goes unpunished.
Do you think this makes any sense?
That bastard Min-gu stabbing me in the back like this.
Seok-ho, you're the only one I have left now.
If I can be of any help to you, Battalion Commander
- I will do anything you ask. - All right.
I was thinking, how would you like to take over Min-gu's position?
Me, sir?
I need someone I can trust, like you, to clean this up.
Otherwise, our battalion's reputation will be in shambles.
Excuse me, Battalion Commander, but may I ask you one thing?
- Of course. - About Min-gu doing this...
Did you really not know about it?
Why?
- Why? Do you think I knew something? - It's just...
The Min-gu I know is greedy for power, not money.
Do you really see me as someone who just uses
And discards his subordinates?
No, sir. That's not it...
It's bad enough that I was stabbed in the back
After trusting him so much
But now I have to be suspected by you as well?
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful in the future.
Now, you have to prove it. That you're much better
Than Min-gu was.
GANGLIM OUTPOST
I heard you went through a lot with Master Sergeant Park.
I mean, how were you brave enough to go see the Regimental Commander?
Since you're in such a difficult situation
I couldn't just stand by and do nothing as an outpost soldier.
But...
On the other hand, I'm worried that I've unnecessarily
- put you in a tough spot. - Well...
It was tough. I got completely torn apart.
I'm sorry. I'll make sure to keep my mouth shut from now on.
You weren't wrong, though.
I'm grateful and I admire what you did, but...
On the other hand, I'm a little worried.
Because there will be people
Who won't like you stepping forward like this.
If you'd be on my side then, Outpost Commander
I think I'd feel really secure.
Okay, I'll be sure to do that.
Thank you.
LIKEABILITY 100%
A colleague has been added.
COLLEAGUE FIRST LIEUTENANT CHO YE-RIN
First Lieutenant Cho Ye-rin.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae. - Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Good work. Thanks to you, things went smoothly.
Not at all, sir. On the contrary
Weren't you put in a difficult position
- because of me? - No.
You did what I couldn't.
Good work. You can go now.
Yes, understood. Salute!
PORK RIND NOODLES
Go on and finish up. Do whatever you want.
You got this! Go on, do it.
What's this? Hey! This is that chicken
Master Sergeant Park ordered for us, right?
Yes. I remembered how much we all enjoyed it last time,
So I tried to make it.
- I'm not sure it'll taste the same. - Give it here.
- My goodness. - Here are rice cakes to go with it.
Of course! How did you make this?
- I just... - Just give it to me.
- Kang Seong-jae! - My goodness! What is it?
It tastes exactly the same. This is so good. How did you do it?
The ingredients that came in this time were much fresher than before
So I think that's what made it possible.
Isn't this a five-star meal?
- Thanks for the food! Thank you. - Enjoy it.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- That looks delicious. - All right, calm down, everyone.
My goodness.
This is seriously so good.
Especially eating the rind and chicken together.
- This is insane. - It'd be perfect chicken with rice.
Oh, so this is the special meal Seong-jae made today.
Yes. For today's special
I made it like the chicken Master Sergeant Park ordered for us.
I tried to copy it as best I could.
Enjoy your food and make sure you clean up properly.
This is delicious.
It's so good.
Darn, Kang Seong-jae, you rascal.
What are we going to do if you make it this delicious?
If it's this good, we'll crave it all the time
But it's not like we can ask you to make it whenever we want.
I'll make it for you personally, sir.
Nah, that won't be happening.
- Enjoy your meal. - Enjoy your meal.
It's so good.
- It's delicious, right? - This is really good.
- It's so good. - I know.
Outpost Commander.
Yes.
One moment.
Wait.
How can you do this so suddenly?
It's not like I have any other choice.
The decision came from up top.
First, we move the personnel.
They say the rest will be sorted out soon, so just be aware of that.
Outposts get shut down all the time these days
So don't read too much into it.
Let's just hurry up and get things in order.
How am I supposed to not read into it?
The issues brought up during the full investigation
Were already found to be nothing
So this can only be seen as retaliation.
Ye-rin, I know you feel this is unfair but...
When something's been decided by the higher-ups
How are we supposed to stop it?
NOTICE OF MILITARY OUTPOST CLOSURE AND REQUEST FOR COOPERATION
But why Ganglim?
I feel like you know the reason better than anyone even if I don't say it.
Hasn't Ganglim always been a problem?
Once this is taken care of
We'll go straight to Army Headquarters.
A new Quest has arrived. Protect the Ganglim Outpost.
Win the division cooking competition.
Failure will result in the closure of the Ganglim Outpost
And The Chef's Path will end.
GANGLIM OUTPOST CLOSURE D-14
THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
They're pulling everyone back to the battalion.
If the outpost disappears, I'll disappear too.
- Win the division cooking competition. - A team of three?
- Our goal is to win. - Start!
Middle!
Hey, let's just quit. We're screwed.
- We will now begin the competition. - Ganglim!
- Yes! - Go show them what Ganglim is made of.
- I thought we'd pulled it off. - Kang Seong-jae!
Snap out of it! Focus!